Guide to the John Boswell Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1959-1996; Series I
  - Westendorf, Leon F. (Lee), 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Westrem, Scott, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - White, Catharine, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Wieseltier, Leon, 1984-1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Williamson, J. Reid, 1969-1994 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Winks, Robin, 1982-1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Wolfson, Evan J., 1990-1994 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Wright, Jerry W., 1990-1992, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Yale University, 1983-1994, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Yo-Z, 1982-1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - ___, Bob, 1969-circa 1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - ___, Buzzy, 1961-1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - ___, Jerry, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, Boswell as academic referee, 1980-1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified, Circa 1970-circa 1993, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Personal files, Circa 1947-2003; Series II
  Arrangement
  The series is arranged in six sections: Biographical, Notebooks, Travel diaries, Creative writing, and Memorabilia, followed by a small number of files that do not fit into those catagories.
  The series is comprised of vital records, passports, report cards, academic transcripts, résumés, commonplace books, travel diaries, student work (high school through graduate school), unpublished fiction writings, published interviews featuring Boswell as the subject, a program and transcript of his memorial service, published obituaries, published and unpublished commemorative writings about him, and memorabilia including diplomas and awards primarily documenting Boswell's personal life. His college and graduate school years, as well as his creative writing efforts through the mid-1980s, are particularly well documented.
  - Biographical
    - General, 1947-1997, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Includes birth certificate, report cards, SAT scores, CVs, academic transcripts, passports, and other items.
    - Newspaper clippings about Boswell, Circa 1962-1994 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
    - Satirical "news" item, Circa 1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Published interviews with Boswell, 1981-1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Same-sex spousal benefits for Yale employees, 1991 March-Jul, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Tributes to Boswell, bound gift book, Circa 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Obituaries, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Commentary on Boswell's death, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Printouts of e-mails sent to Patricia Boswell.
    - Commentary on Boswell's work, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Printouts of e-mails and web pages.
    - Commemoration, 1994-2003, undated (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
    - Memorial Service, 1995 February (Box 18, Folder 5-7)
    - Hexter, Ralph J. (Literary Executor), 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Consists of Hexters correspondence regarding Boswell after Boswell's death.
  - Notebooks
    - Regarding Catholicism, Circa 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
      Includes Boswell's writings about Catholicism and newspaper clippings interleaved.
    - Regarding homosexuality, Undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Circa 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Circa 1987 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Travel diaries, 1980 March-1993 (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
    Travel diaries are arranged chronologically.
  - Student work
    - Undergraduate papers, 1965-1969, undated (Box 20, Folder 5-7)
    - Published creative writing
      - "The Moldau," William and Mary Review, 1966 spring (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - "Stop Treating Us Like Kids," The Episcopalian, 1967 October (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - "Poem," William and Mary Review, 1969 winter (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Undergraduate notes, spiral bound, 1965-1969 (Box 21, Folder 3-8)
    - Undergraduate honors thesis, 1969 May (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Graduate school exams and papers, 1969-1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Graduate school papers, 1970, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Graduate school notes, spiral bound, 1969 September-December (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Doctoral dissertation and related correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Creative writing
    - Untitled, Circa 1965-circa 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - "The Murmurs", 1972-1973? (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - "The Murmurs," notes for book on lying, Circa 1972-circa 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - "Ancient science", Circa 1972 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - "Mac & Bob," "Art & Thom," "Point & Buck", Circa 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - "Art & Thom," "Mac & Bob," etc., Circa 1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - "A Miscellany", Circa 1973 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - Untitled (regarding Pere, Josep, and Alicia in Barcelona, 1410), Circa 1984 (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
    - Untitled (story of Marra and Fatima), Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous notes, Circa 1969-1988, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Memorabilia
    - Academic honors, 1959-1968, 1992 October (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Includes Phi Beta Kappa, Pi Delta Epsilon, and other notices of academic honors and distinction.
    - Artwork (oversize), Circa 1955-1965 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Artwork and clippings (oversize), Circa 1960 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Awards and degrees (oversize), 1969, 1975 1980, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Award, Yale teaching (posthumous), 1995 May (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Playscript (student play in which Boswell acted), Circa 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Photographs and portrait (drawing), 1988 Jun, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Oversize photograph, Undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Programs, 1962, 1965, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Slides, photographs (Southern Spain, Oxford, Paris, etc.), 1972-1973, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Humor, 1972-1992, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Saints, etc. (artwork), Undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, Circa 1956-circa 1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Computer files, 1994 December (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Notes on contents of Boswell's computer files, compiled by Jim Meehan
  - Floppy disk directories, 1980-1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Linguist's software - receipts, 1990-1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - List of books given to HGS Library, Circa 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Professional files, Circa 1970-2004; Series III
  The series is arranged in three section: Writings and presentations, Teaching files, and Subject files, followed by miscellaneous reprints and notecards.
  The series is comprised of manuscripts of Boswell's numerous publications, teaching materials (including lectures, presentations, notes on 3x5" index cards, syllabi and course packs), photocopies of foreign language source materials, research notes (also on 3x5" index cards), offprints of scholarly articles by Boswell and others, reviews of his books, cassette tapes of a 1983 lecture on gays and Christianity, Boswell's draft reviews of others scholars' books and manuscripts, and documents related to petitions in legal cases concerning gay and lesbian military officers. Of particular interest is the extensive documentation of his scholarly efforts, especially source materials, partial and complete drafts, correspondence with publishers and from readers, and research notes. By far the most voluminous such documentation concerns Christianity, Social Tolerance, and Homosexuality. Also included here are notes on and drafts of various papers delivered at scholarly conferences throughout the 1980s and into the 1990s. Numerous photocopies of foreign language source materials thoroughly document obscure aspects of European church history from the Middle Ages, notably attitudes toward and dogma concerning marriage, homosexuals, and homosexuality. Other foreign language source materials document attitudes toward and examples of the abandonment of children in Europe from antiquity to the Renaissance. There are no paper drafts of Same-Sex Unions, The Kindness of Strangers, or The Royal Treasure.
  Additional writings can be found in Series IV, Electronic files. The electronic files include drafts of articles, book chapters, lectures, presentations, and Same-Sex Unions.
  - Writings and presentations
    Arranged by type and chronologically therein.
    The section consists of project files for books, articles, reviews, talks, and presentations. Project files includes correspondence, research material, drafts, manuscripts, as well as printed copies. Some project files do not contain the work itself.
    - Books
      - The Royal Treasure
        - Research notebooks
          The notebooks include notes and copies of documents and articles.
          - Medieval Spanish councils, Circa 1973-1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
          - "F MISC/2 903/906 KEY", Circa 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
          - Crown of Aragon archive registers, Circa 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
          - Registers, Circa 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
          - "El Judice de la Cancillería Real: Registros", Circa 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
          - Notes for Royal Treasure [?], Circa 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
          - Crown of Aragon archive, Circa 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
          - "SP/ART.S", Circa 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
        - Note cards, Undated (Box 29)
        - Reviews, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Christianity, Social Tolerance, and Homosexuality
        - Correspondence
          - Yale University Press, 1976, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 1)
          - University of Chicago Press, 1978-1982, undated (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
          - Libraries and museums, regarding figures and illustration, 1978-1979, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
            Includes notes.
          - European libraries regarding photostats of medieval manuscripts, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 5)
          - Readers
            - General, 1979-1981, undated (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
            - Appreciation, 1980-1989 (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
            - Bibliographic suggestions, 1980-1988, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
            - Regarding patristic interpretations of Romans 1, 1981-1990, undated (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
            - Corrections, 1982-1986 (Box 31, Folder 7)
          - Related projects
            - French translation, 1980-1985, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
            - TV series (proposed), 1982-1986, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - Drafts
          - Working draft, Circa 1978 (Box 32, Folder 2-6)
          - Rejected portions, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
            Also includes correspondence from Ralph Hexter, May - June 1976.
          - Rejected pages, notes, Circa 1978 (Box 33, Folder 3-5)
        - Reviews and publicity
          - Notices, 1979 May-1986 September (Box 33, Folder 6)
          - Awards and responses, 1980-1986 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
          - Reviews, interviews, and related literature, 1974-1993, undated (Box 34, Folder 3-5)
            Includes some correspondence.
          - Reviews, interviews, and related literature, 1980-1993, undated (Box 35, Folder 1-5)
        - Research material
          - Subjects
            - General (photocopies), Undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
            - Gays and religion, 1973-1988, undated (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
            - Gay history (letters, articles, conference schedules, reviews), 1976-1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)
            - Gay philosophy (correspondence and typescripts), 1980 January-1984 Apr, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
            - Greek plays, etc., Circa 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
            - Greek sources, Circa 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
            - Male homosexuality in the Middle Ages (offprints, and photocopies), 1981-1988, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
            - Petrus Damiani, Liber Gomorrhianus (translated by Ralph J. Hexter), Circa 1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
            - "Quam Pravus mos," Latin poem translation, Circa 1980 (Box 36, Folder 7)
            - Twelfth-century literature concerning homosexuality (photocopies), Circa 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 8)
          - Notes, Undated (Box 37)
            On 3x5" index cards.
          - Miscellaneous notes, Circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 1)
          - Miscellaneous offprints, 1977-1993 (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
      - Untitled, on Jews in Medieval Spain?
        - Binder 1, Circa 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 4)
          Includes photocopies, draft introduction, notes and conference proceedings.
        - Binder 2, Circa 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 5)
          Includes drafts, chapter on converts to Judaism and notes.
        - Notebook, Circa 1981 August (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Notes and permissions to research and copy documents in Europe, 1981 March-July (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Photoreproductions from German libraries, 1981 July-August (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Homosexuality in Europe (proposed)
        - Proposal, contract and notes, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Borchardt, Georges, correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - The Kindness of Strangers
        - Correspondence
          - General, 1980-1988, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
          - Agent and publisher, 1987-1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
          - Readers' reports, 1987 Aug, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Illustrations, 1979-1991, undated (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
        - Index, draft, Circa 1989 (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Related projects "Expositio and Oblatio"
          Contains material on works derived by Boswell from The Kindness of Strangers. Includes journal articles and public lectures.
          - New England Medieval Conference presentation, 1980 October (Box 39, Folder 11)
          - Article submitted to the American Historical Review, 1981-1984 (Box 39, Folder 12-13)
          - Article submitted to the American Historical Review, 1981-1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
          - Notes for public presentations, 1982-1986 (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - Reviews and publicity, 1988-1994, undated (Box 40, Folder 3-4)
        - Research material
          - General
            Includes photocopies of source material and notes.
            - Binder, untitled, Circa 1980s (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
            - Binder, untitled (continued), Circa 1980s (Box 41, Folder 1)
            - Articles and notes, 1985-1992, undated (Box 41, Folder 2-5)
          - Ancient sources, Circa 1980s (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
          - Early Middle Ages sources, Circa 1980s (Box 42, Folder 3)
          - High Middle Ages sources, Circa 1980s (Box 42, Folder 4)
          - Low Middle Ages sources and notes, Circa 1983 (Box 42, Folder 5)
          - Medieval sources, Circa 1980s (Box 42, Folder 6)
          - Modern analogues, Circa 1980s (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
          - Patres, Circa 1980s (Box 43, Folder 3)
          - Putting out (abandonment), binder, Circa 1980s (Box 43, Folder 4-7)
          - Semichon, Ernest, Histoire des Enfants Abandonnés, Circa 1980s (Box 43, Folder 8)
          - Notes, Undated (Box 44–45)
      - Same-Sex Unions in Premodern Europe
        - Correspondence
          - General, 1990 July-1992 January (Box 46, Folder 1)
          - Mitchell, Doug (University of Chicago Press), 1993 February-Apr, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
          - O'Neill, Father Dennis B., 1989 February-1993 January (Box 46, Folder 3)
        - Copy-editing notes, 1993 September-Nov, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - Illustrations, 1979-1993 (Box 46, Folder 5-7)
        - Reviews and publicity
          Includes notes and some correspondence.
          - Current debates and related book reviews, 1985-1994, undated (Box 46, Folder 8-9)
          - Reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 10-11)
            Includes correspondence.
          - Reviews and cartoons, 1994-2004, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
          - Poster (Box 89, Folder 1)
        - Research material
          Contains correspondence, photocopies of articles, newsclippings, notes, and results of database searches. Arranged by type and alphabetically within each type.
          - Binders
            Contains material removed from three-ring binders. Includes correspondence, notes, and photocopies on specified topics.
            - "ADEL.MSS", Undated (Box 47, Folder 2-6)
            - "Alii Sancti" (saints), Circa 1989 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
            - "Heterosexuality", Circa 1991 (Box 48, Folder 3-4)
              Contents concern heterosexual marriage liturgy.
            - "Historica", 1984-1991, undated (Box 48, Folder 5-7)
              Contains correspondence, notes, and photocopies.
            - "Hist Mod", Circa 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
              Contents concern sources from Middle Ages.
            - "Pobratim", Circa 1991 (Box 49, Folder 4-5)
              Contents concern same-sex union liturgy.
            - Scripta, 1987-1992 (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
              Contains notes for presentations, notes, correspondence and bibliographies.
            - Serge and Bacchus (2 binders), 1985-1990, undated (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
            - "Texts", 1989-1990, undated (Box 50, Folder 4-7)
              Contains transcriptions and translations of sources as well as correspondence.
          - Database searches
            - Greek text excerpts from database search of "FRAT", Circa 1988 (Box 50, Folder 8)
            - Greek text search in database for 'αγαπ (agap), Circa 1988 (Box 51, Folder 1-4)
            - Greek text search in database and Ibycus word processing tutorial, Circa 1988 (Box 51, Folder 5)
            - Greek excerpts from database search, 1988 July (Box 51, Folder 6)
            - Greek text excerpts from database search Sundesm and Sund, Undated (Box 51, Folder 7-8)
            - Pandora search for the Thesaurus Linguae Graecae (TLG), 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 9)
          - Source material/Subject files
            Contains photocopies and notes.
            - Ancient churches, Circa 1992 (Box 51, Folder 10)
            - Ancient sources, Circa 1991 September (Box 51, Folder 11)
            - Antinaus, Greek source material, Circa 1991 (Box 52, Folder 1)
            - Bagaos, Greek source material, Circa 1991 (Box 52, Folder 2)
            - "Barberini Grec 336", Circa 1990 (Box 52, Folder 3)
            - Belgian library, 1992 April (Box 52, Folder 4)
            - Brotherhood
              - Adel, Circa 1980s (Box 52, Folder 5)
              - Adel-gen, 1982-1991, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
              - Adelph. pending, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 7)
              - Patres, Circa 1992 November (Box 52, Folder 8)
              - Patres: Frater, Circa 1992 (Box 52, Folder 9)
              - Rites, Circa 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 10)
              - Russian, Circa 1990, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
            - Ceremonies, texts from Vatican Film Library, 1990 January-1992 December (Box 52, Folder 12)
            - Cosmas and Damian, Circa 1992 (Box 52, Folder 13)
            - Cyrus and John, Circa 1992 (Box 52, Folder 14)
            - Gays and religion, 1981-1988, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
            - Greek liturgy, Circa 1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
            - Head, Thomas, "The Marriages of Christina of Markyate", 1990 (Box 53, Folder 3)
            - Homosexuality, male and Christianity, Circa 1989-1992 July (Box 53, Folder 4)
            - Humphrey and Saladdin, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 5)
            - Marriage
              - General, brotherhood, history of sexuality, 1991-1992, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
              - Common law codes, Circa 1989 (Box 53, Folder 7)
              - Gay and general, Circa 1989-1993 (Box 53, Folder 8)
              - Heterosexual marriage, St. Thomas Aquinas, Saint Basil, and others on, Circa 1988-1990 (Box 53, Folder 9)
              - Human Relations Area Files, sources from, 1989 Apr, undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
              - Same-sex marriage/brotherhood, Circa 1991 (Box 53, Folder 11)
              - Same-sex marriage, modern analogues of adelphopoeia, 1987-1992, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
            - Medieval liturgy, Circa 1990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
            - Phillip and Bartholomew, Greek text excerpts, Circa 1990-1991 (Box 54, Folder 2)
            - Polyeuct, Circa 1992 (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
            - "Serge and Bacchus," annotated translation by Ralph Hexter, 1992 December-1993 November (Box 54, Folder 5)
            - Serge and Bacchus, lives of, Circa 1990 (Box 54, Folder 6)
            - Saints' lives in the Middle Ages (correspondence, source material), 1987 December-1992 December (Box 54, Folder 7)
            - Same-sex love in Medieval period, Circa 1992 (Box 54, Folder 8)
            - Spiritual brotherhood in early Middle Ages, 1987 Apr, circa 1992 (Box 54, Folder 9)
            - Theodore Stratelates and Tiron, Circa 1992 (Box 54, Folder 10)
            - Typica, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 11-12)
            - Typica (continued), 1991 (Box 55, Folder 1)
            - Women, 1987 Oct, undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
          - Articles for research concerning same-sex relations and unions in antiquity and the Middle Ages, Circa 1991
            Arranged alphabetically by author's last name.
            - A-B, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 3)
            - C, Circa 1991 June (Box 55, Folder 4)
            - Chénon, Emile, Circa 1991 (Box 55, Folder 5)
            - D, Circa 1991 (Box 55, Folder 6)
            - E-G, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 7)
            - H-J, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 8)
            - K, Circa 1991 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
            - L-M, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 3)
            - N-O, 1990, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
            - P, Circa 1991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
            - R-S, Circa 1991 (Box 56, Folder 6-7)
            - Schwerdtfeger, Circa 1991 (Box 56, Folder 8)
            - T-V, Circa 1991 (Box 56, Folder 9)
            - W, Circa 1991 (Box 57, Folder 1)
          - Notes, photocopied articles, primary sources, Circa 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 2-5)
          - Miscellaneous notes and correspondence, 1992 July-Nov, undated (Box 57, Folder 6-7)
        - Writings by others incorporating Same-Sex Unions in Premodern Europe, 1995, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Unhappy Family (aka Religions of Spain)
        - Correspondence, notes, 1976-1983, 1993, undated (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
        - Chapter drafts, 1993 August (Box 58, Folder 3)
        - Binders, research materials
          Consists of articles and other writings by others.
          - "Unhappy Fam., art. 1", 1993 (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
          - "Unhapp. Fam., arts. 2", Circa 1993 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Articles and book chapters (non-fiction)
      - "Altercatio Ganimedis et Hebe": Edition, Translation and Commentary, 1977 Apr, 1981 Feb, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Intellectual Slippage, 1980-1988, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - "A Crucial Juncture: An Address to the 1980 Integrity Convention," Integrity Forum (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Ancient Sexuality, 1981 April-Jun, undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - "Revolutions, Universals, and Sexual Categories," Salmagundi, 1981 August-1983 May (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Minorities in the Middle Ages, 1985 Nov, undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Homosexuality/Heterosexuality: The Kinsey Scale and Current Research, 1986 June-August (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - "Not Everything Falls Under 'Free Speech,'" Yale Daily News, 1986 September 30 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - "AIDS and Sex: An Integrated Biomedical and Biobehavioral Approach", 1987 December (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - "All Fall Down," The New Journal, 1987 December (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - "Sexual and Ethical Categories in Premodern Europe", Circa 1988 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - "Glaser, Forward", 1988 January (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - "Homosexuality and Religious Life", 1988 Jan, undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - "Aragon and the Mediterranean in the Fourteenth Century" in New Cambridge Medical History, 1988 October-1995 Mar, undated (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - "Jews, Bicycle Riders, and Gay People," Yale Journal of Law and the Humanities, 1989 May (Box 59, Folder 13)